triptogether.com 2018-08-13

# Privacy Policy - Triptogether.com

To complete your registration, please click on the confirmation link we have sent to Resend confirmation

The confirmation message has been resent to

Your email has been confirmed. Thank you for being a part of TripTogether!

Going to ? Why don’t you create your own trip to find travelmates faster!

×

TripTogether Jaga Smart tech, Corp.

FREE - On the App Store

Depending on what you do when you visit any Web site, you are providing information about your visit to the site’s operators. This includes TripTogether.com. We value privacy and think you do too, so we want you to have the information you need to make your own decisions about your personal privacy. When you visit or supply information to any Web site, we think it’s a good idea for you to first understand what that site’s privacy policies are. If the site doesn’t tell you, don’t hesitate to ask.

The bottom line at www.TripTogether.com is that we only use the information that we get from your visit for internal tracking purposes, to make TripTogether.com as useful and interesting to you as we can, and to respond to your requests for information or other services. Except for as specifically noted, we do not use your personal information for any other purpose; we never sell it to any third party; and we never share it with any third party, other than as otherwise provided in this policy. TripTogether.com utilizes Google Shopping Cart API, which is subject to google.com’s privacy policy (http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/), incorporated by reference herein.

Read more about how your personal information is managed:

Notice
    What personal information we collect and how we use your information. Our policy regarding information sharing.
Choice
    How you can decide what communication you’ll receive from us.
Access
    How you can control the use of your personal information.
Security
    How we protect the security of your personal information.
Customer Service and Recourse

Changes to the TripTogether.com Privacy Policy.

How to contact TripTogether.com.

## Notice

What personal information we collect: 
     When you visit the TripTogether.com Web site, we capture the Internet provider’s domain name and country that you came from (e.g., 'aol.com') and the paths taken as you move from page to page (i.e., your «click stream» activity). 
Visitor Registration or Requests for Information:
     TripTogether.com only collects personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using or registering with the TripTogether.com site. «Personal information» includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name or email address; and, in the case of affiliate agreements, your name and company name. While you can browse our site without registering, you will need to register in order to take advantage of certain features. 
Browsing and the use of Cookies:

TripTogether.com uses cookie technology as part of our Web site’s statistical reporting. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a Web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer’s browser. It holds information a site may need to personalize your experience (i.e., rotating images on TripTogether.com home page) and to gather Web site statistical data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded, the internet provider’s domain name and country that our visitors come from (e.g. 'aol.com,' or 'umich.edu') and the addresses of sites visited immediately before, and after, coming to TripTogether.com. However, none of this is associated with you as an individual. It is measured only in aggregate. The information in the cookies lets us trace your «click stream» activity (i.e., the paths taken by visitors to our site as they move from page to page. Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you.

We also use standard Web server log files to help us count visitors and evaluate our site’s technical capacity. We use this information to find out how many people visit TripTogether.com, help us arrange the pages in the most user-friendly way, keep the site browser-friendly, and to make our pages more useful to our visitors. We record information on site traffic but not information on individual visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular will be kept or used.

To browse without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the «Help» menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)

How we may use information we collect:

We may use information to:

  * Arrange the Web site in the most user-friendly way;
  * Fulfill your requests for products and services;
  * Customize your browsing experience of this Web site;
  * Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices;
  * Manage your account and your preferences;
  * Analyze use of and improve our website, products and services;
  * Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our website;
  * Respond to your question or suggestions.

Email, Mailing Lists, and Other Services: 

When you send us an email, we use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use.

You may also daily receive any combination of our email newsletters, account updates, or special offers targeted to your interests sent to you by  TripTogether.com

Please be aware that scammers sometimes create fake emails or fake accounts that look like they’re from TripTogether. These emails often:

  * Offer things that sound too good to be true (For example: You’ve won the TripTogether Lottery)
  * Asking you for money for customs tax
  * Claim to be a TripTogether administrator or staff

If any email looks suspicious do not click any of the links in it, open any attachments or respond to that messages. Please forward the email directly to [support@triptogether.com](mailto:support@triptogether.com) in order for our team to look into it further.

Linking To Other Sites:

Please remember that when you use a link to go from TripTogether.com to another Web site, the TripTogether.com Site Rules and this Privacy Policy are no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including any site that has a link on TripTogether.com, is subject to the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

Our policy regarding sharing of information:

Service Providers: We also may disclose information to outside companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer. For example, we may work with an outside company to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist us in distributing emails; (c) assist us with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide us storage and analysis; (d) provide fraud prevention; and (e) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We require that these outside companies agree to keep confidential all information we share with them and to use the information only to perform their obligations in our agreements with them.

Other Companies: We may provide information to carefully selected outside companies when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you.

Business Transitions: We may transfer or share a copy of personal information about you in the event that TripTogether.com or one of its properties, affiliates, or subsidiaries goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets.

Compliance with Law: We may provide access to information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, to limit our legal liability, and to protect our rights or to protect the rights, property, or safety of visitors of this website or the public.

Age Restrictions
    Children under eighteen years of age are prohibited from using Our Websites. We do not target our sites or services to children under the age of 18, and in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we may receive from users we believe to be under the age of 18 will be purged from our database.

## Choice

Choice/Opt-Out

TripTogether.com may periodically send you email messages describing updates, new features, or promotional offers related to this Web site. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time.

To unsubscribe email us at [support@triptogether.com](mailto:support@triptogether.com). You can also follow the 'unsubscribe' instructions and link provided with each email or as we otherwise provide.

## Access

Updating Your Information

To modify or delete your personal information, simply follow the instructions:

  1. Log into your account;
  2. Select My Account on TripTogether.com´s Main Page;
  3. Scroll down and select My Profile;
  4. Edit your personal information;
  5. Select Save.

Also you can send your request to our Support Team, and we will make the requested changes.

## Security

The security of your personal information is very important to us and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. TripTogether.com uses firewalls and has security measures in place at its physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Web site.

TripTogether.com has VeriSign and McAfee secure certificates demonstrating that the site is fully tested, approved and certified by these two leading security systems. You are protected from any virus, identity theft, credit card fraud, spyware, spam, or online scam on our site.

## Customer Service and Recourse

Contacting the Website

Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any TripTogether.com related services, you consent to TripTogether.com's processing of this information in the United States/Russia as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating.

If you have any questions, comments or complaints about TripTogether.com's privacy policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to contact our Customer Support:

Acceptance of Privacy Statement

Your use of our website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy statement and the applicable Terms and Conditions. By using our website, you are accepting the practices set out in this privacy statement and the applicable TripTogether.com Terms of Use Agreement by using our website, you represent and warrant that you will not create any databases, websites, software, legal entities and services competitive with TripTogether.com. Such activity will be investigated, and appropriate legal action will be taken, including without limitation, civil, criminal, and injunctive redress.

TripTogether.com reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. We take privacy matters very seriously, and intend to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. We will occasionally update our privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy policy updates.

Company address
    
Effective Date

This privacy statement was last revised on October 21, 2016.

<https://www.triptogether.com/privacy-policy/>

##  Make your profile more visible  
with Premium Membership only for  Become a Premium Member  
to boost your profile only for  Confirm your subscription  
to continue your journey for only 

CVC2/CVV2

The security code is a 3 or 4 digit code printed on your credit card. We require this code as a security measure to our customers. Requiring this information helps to ensure that the credit card is present at the time of purchase. If you cannot find this code, or it is illegible, please contact your credit card issuer.

## Congrats, traveler!

Now you are a Premium Plus member of TripTogether! 

Time to start your adventure!

##  Grab Premium Membership! Confirm your subscription to continue your journey Add super features for $ only 

premium membership 

$ /month

premium plus membership 

$ /month

CVC2/CVV2

The security code is a 3 or 4 digit code printed on your credit card. We require this code as a security measure to our customers. Requiring this information helps to ensure that the credit card is present at the time of purchase. If you cannot find this code, or it is illegible, please contact your credit card issuer.

__ premium membership 

  * Special badge of a verified user
  * More attention from users

__ premium plus membership 

  * New profile look
  * Big photo in search results
  * "See" all verified users
  * “Read” message indicator
  * Special badge of a verified user 
  * “Last seen” user indicator
  * Cool new emoticons

## Congrats, traveler!

Now you are a Premium Plus member of TripTogether! 

Time to start your adventure!

##  Are you sure you want to lose all Premium features   
and become an average traveler? 

##  Are you sure you want to lose all Premium features   
and become an average traveler? 

__ premium membership 

  * Special badge of a verified user
  * More attention from users

__ premium plus membership 

  * New profile look
  * Big photo in search results
  * "See" all verified users
  * “Read” message indicator
  * Special badge of a verified user 
  * “Last seen” user indicator
  * Cool new emoticons

  * Hue 0deg
  * Saturation 100%
  * Brightness 100%
  * Contrast 100%

You will never get any messages from blocked user

### Whoa!

**This person has gone on vacation!**

## I Want to Travel With

##  Enter destinations

## Travel dates

### Change your password

## Create a new password you can easily remember!

Why not create your own trip?  
It’s the easiest way to find travel mates to join you!

## Hello Recipient Name,

Sender Name has left you a message on TripTogether.

The first 40 symbols of message...

TripTogether.com

## Hello Recipient Name,

Sender Name has left you a message on TripTogether.

The first 40 symbols of message...

TripTogether.com

## Welcome to TripTogether!

To complete your registration, please click on the confirmation link we have sent to

Resend confirmation

The confirmation message has been resent to

## 

It's

her (his) 

birthday today

Add your date of birth and gender years,  __

Lives in

add your hometown []() __

Works as

add your occupation __

Knows

add languages you speak __

____ Add to Remove from Favorites

I would like to travel with

describe your potential travel mate __

###  Plan your trip  trip to find the perfect travel buddy! Choose a destination, enter a date and invite travelers to join you.

####  has no travel plans yet.

Chat with  to find out where the traveler may like to go.

###  Create a new story! Tell other travelers about your last trip or about the place you live in!

####  has not shared any travel experience.

Chat with  and find out which places the traveler has been to.

User Settings

###  Plan your trip to find the perfect travel buddy! Choose a destination, enter a date and invite travelers to join you.

####  Become the discoverer! Be the first to travel to this location!

###  Create a new story! Tell other travelers about your last trip or about the place you live in!

####  Be the first to write a story about this place.

Introduce Yourself to other Travel Mates! 

Add photo Upload a photo from your computer

or

UPLOAD PHOTO FROM YOUR COMPUTER UPLOAD FROM DEVICE

Or drag them into this area Drop photos here

## Save your changes

You can save changed texts by pressing **Ctrl+Shift+Enter**

## Welcome

You can enter operator mode by pressing gear button in the top panel.
